&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：现在我们有了基础。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: So now we have the foundation in place.
我们可以理解我们谈论的对象
We can understand what object we're talking about
当我们绑定到这个关键字时。
when we bind to this key word.
让我们看看我们可以用它做些什么。
Let's look at what we can do with it.
我们将首先关注班级模式，因为它是
We're gonna to focus first on the class pattern since it is
到目前为止，JavaScript中使用的最流行的模式。
by far the most prevalent pattern used in JavaScript.
class关键字表面上是层叠在
The class keyword is ostensibly syntactic sugar layered on top of
原型系统，我们将在下一步学习。
the prototype system, which we will learn about next.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：看起来是这样的。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: So here's what it looks like.
我们使用class关键字，我们使用class关键字的名称。
We use a class keyword, we use a name for the class keyword.
顺便说一下，这是一个众所周知的事实。
By the way, this is a little know fact.
类不必是语句，类可以是表达式，并且
Classes don't have to be statements, classes can be expressions, and
他们可以是匿名的。
they can be anonymous.
我从来不认为你应该做一个匿名的类表达式，但是
I don't ever think you should do an anonymous class expression but
这实际上是一件事。
that is actually a thing.
定义类时可以使用扩展子句，也可以不使用扩展子句。
Classes can be defined with or without an extends clause.
在这里，我们只是定义了一个不扩展任何内容的类，所以
Here, we're just defining a class that doesn't extend anything, so
这是顶级班级。
it's the top level class.
如果愿意，您可以选择定义一个构造函数，就像我们在第2行所做的那样，
You can choose to define a constructor if you want, like we're doing on line 2,
您可以添加方法。
and you can add methods.
看一下第4行，它们之间甚至不需要逗号。
And look on line 4, we don't even need commas in between them.
他们做了一件了不起的工作，只是运球各种句法糖分
They did a fantastic job of just dribbling all kinds of syntactic sugar
在这个功能上。
on this feature.
非常吸引人。
It's very attractive.
然后我们看一下第10行，它看起来完全像在其他任何地方实例化类
Then we look at line 10, it looks exactly like instantiating classes in any other
面向类的语言。
class oriented language.
我们只是说新的，大写的W工作坊，我们得到了一个实例。
We just say new, capital W Workshop, and we get an instance.
我们调用Deep JS.ask，方法调用起作用。
And we call deepJS.ask and the method call works.
这里有一个有用的上下文。
And there's a this context that works.
这就是类语法的样子。
So that's what the class syntax looks like.
如果要将一个类扩展到另一个类，
If you want to extend one class into another class,
您可以在第10行使用扩展子句，如下所示。
you use the extends clause like here on line 10.
您不必重新定义任何其他方法
You don't have to redefine any other methods that
已经定义了，因为它们将被称为继承。
are already defined because they'll be so called inherited.
因此，您可以定义新方法，如第11行上的SpeakUp方法
So you can define new methods like the speakUp method here on line 11 and
当您实例化该Child类时，您可以调用第18行，
when you instantiate that Child class, you can then invoke line 18,
你可以调用那个方法，点说话，就像它在对象上一样。
you can invoke that method, dot speak up, exactly like it was on the object.
事实上，班级系统现在也有一个超级关键字，
As a matter of fact, the class system also now has a super keyword in it,
这允许你做相对多态。
which allows you to do relative polymorphism.
如果您有一个定义与父类同名的方法的子类，
If you have a child class that defines a method of the same name as a parent class,
所谓的影子。
so called shadowing.
如果您在子级中定义了与父级中相同的方法名称。
If you have one that defines the same method name in a child as in the parent.
您可以从子引用父
You can refer to the parent from the child
通过说超级圆点，就像你在第12行看到的那样。
by saying super dot, like you see on line 12.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：顺便说一下，这是一个扩展到
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: By the way, this is an example of extension beyond
因为在ES6类之前，
syntactic sugar because prior to ES6 classes,
基本上没有办法做相对多态性。
there was essentially no way to do relative polymorphism.
没有超级关键字的等价物。
There was no equivalent of the super keyword.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：我不是说这是件坏事，我只是说，
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: I'm not saying that's a bad thing, I'm just saying,
当人们说，这只是语法糖，不，它不是。
when people say, it's just syntactic sugar anyway, no, it isn't.
这是它自己的机制，有它自己的一套复杂性。
It's its whole own mechanism, with its own set of complexities.
如果你注意到规格，有一大堆东西，
And if you pay attention to the specs at all, there's a whole bunch of stuff,
就像一列去上课的大货车。
like a big freight train headed for classes.
它会爆炸出各种新的复杂性，私人和公共领域，而且
It's gonna explode with all kinds of new complexity, private and public fields, and
私人的和公共的方法，以及所有其他的，装饰师和
private and public methods, and all these others, decorators and
所有这些其他的东西。
all this other stuff.
因此类是它们自己的复杂性同步。
So classes are their own complexity sync.
他们会加入各种各样的新功能。
They're gonna get all kinds of new features added into them.
在这一点上，它就像是一种语言中的一种语言，它不仅仅是句法上的糖，
It's like a language within a language at this point, it's not just syntactic sugar,
但对于这些最简单的例子来说，这是一个有用的心智模型。
but that is a useful, mental model for these simplest of examples.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：我不得不这么说，尽管有一大堆句法
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: I do have to say that even though there's a bunch of syntactic
糖，他们并没有从根本上改变
sugar, they didn't change anything fundamentally about how
函数调用工作以及如何绑定此关键字。
function calls work and how that this keyword gets bound.
因此，即使您在类实例上定义了一个方法，
So, even if you define a method on a class instance,
如果你把它传递到一个所说的超时，你猜怎么着？
if you pass it into a said timeout, guess what?
它会失去这种束缚。
It's gonna lose its this binding.
它们不是神奇的自动绑定。
They're not somehow magically auto bound.
类上的那些函数，
Those functions on class,
类实例上的方法的行为就像任何其他函数一样。
the methods on class instances, behave just like any other function.
有很多开发人员对这个决定感到不安，
And there are a lot of developers that were upset at that decision,
他们真的希望JavaScript更进一步，强制类
they really wanted JavaScript to go one step further and force class
方法是按照它们在普通类中的方式自动绑定的，或者
methods to be sort of autobound the way they are in normal class or
在更传统的面向类的语言中。
in more traditional class orientated languages.
这种自动绑定这个方法的想法就是为什么在这个过渡时期
And that idea of having an autobound this method is why in this interim period for
在过去的几年里，我们看到了模式的爆炸式增长
the last several years, we have seen an explosion of patterns where
人们想要硬绑定或自动绑定的方法，但它们不是自动的。
people want hardbound or autobound methods and they aren't automatically.
所以你看到的很多事情就像第四条线，
So what you see a lot happening is something like line four,
我们没有在原型上定义方法，而是添加到
where instead of defining a method on the prototype, we added into
构造函数并使用硬绑定方法或使用箭头函数，好吗？
the constructor and use a hardbound method or use an arrow function, okay?
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：看到这个成语的传播，我深感不安。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: This deeply troubles me to see this propagation of this idiom.
这种想法，它必须是硬绑定的。
This idea that it's got to be hard bound.
我不想让它有任何动态性，所以我将使用词法this
I don't want any dynamism to it all, so I'm gonna use a lexical this
来自箭头函数，或者我将使用硬绑定函数来实现这一点。
from an arrow function or I'm gonna use a hard bound function to accomplish that.
因为你在本质上背叛了类构建的整个系统。
Because you are essentially betraying the entire system that classes has built upon.
整个类系统都是基于这种思想构建的，而您的方法并不存在于此之上
The entire class system is built upon this idea that your methods don't exist on
您的实例，它们存在于您的原型和
your instances, they exist on your prototypes and
猜猜当你说this.ask并给它分配一个函数时会发生什么？
guess what happens when you say this.ask and you assign it a function?
它不再在原型上，而是在您的实例上。
It's no longer on the prototype anymore, it's on your instance.
所以每次你实例化一个函数，你就得到了一个完整的
So every single time you instantiate a function, you're getting a whole
添加到每个单个实例的所有这些函数的单独副本。
separate copy of all those functions added to every single instance.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：这并不是特别糟糕
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: It's not that that is particularly terrible for
性能，因为JavaScript引擎实际上非常擅长这一点。
performance cuz JavaScript engines are actually pretty good at it.
我真正的问题是
The real problem I have with that is it's
就像我们在这个关键词里说的那样。
exactly like we talked about in this key word.
你会不厌其烦地做这些语法上的杂耍
You're going to all the trouble to do all this syntactic juggling
用这个关键字让你自己得到一个可以是超级动态的类系统。
to get yourself a class system with this key word that can be super dynamic.
猜猜你刚刚创建了什么，一个非常糟糕的模块版本。
And guess what you just created, a really terrible version of the module.
一个真正令人困惑，丑陋，脆弱的词汇模块版本。
A really confusing, and ugly, and brittle version of a lexical module.
我们已经有20多年的词汇模块模式。
We've had lexical module pattern for 20 plus years.
我们应该只是拥抱和
And we ought to just be embracing and
使用语言中已经存在的内容。
using what was already there in the language.
这并不是说对班级制度没有好处。
That's not to say there's no benefit to the class system.
肯定有好处。
There are definitely benefits.
如果你真的想做多态和多层次的遗传
If you really wanna do polymorphism and multiple levels of inheritance and
超级等等。
super and all that.
班级制度很棒。
The class system is great.
只是绝大多数使用阶级系统的人，
It's just that the vast majority of people that are using the class system,
最后在它的膝盖处完全切断了它。
end up completely cutting it off at its knees.
切断它的膝盖，失去所有的动态灵活性，并得到
Cutting it off its knees, losing all the dynamic flexibility, and getting
对于模块模式来说，这是一个非常糟糕的版本。
a really terrible version of what they could have had with the module pattern.